When I was a child,
I fell off the jungle gym and broke my leg.
Ever since, I've had a terrible fear of heights.
I turned into a completely indoor person,
and got into hobbies that I could enjoy alone.
I had fewer friends, but I thought that it didn't bother me,
and yet...
Let's climb the mountain together as we promised!
Come over to my house. Let's make plans!
Wait...
Anything but mountains!
Second Ascent
Let's Go Together!
I'm home!
Hey, Aoi-chan.
You've grown, haven't you?
Aoi,
over here!
My father's climbing gear.
Isn't it amazing?
Let's use these to climb the mountain, like we promised!
You can't climb something like that right away.
You'd be surprised how many people get hurt or lost.
You said we could go once we were in high school!
You need to learn the ropes first!
Do you know what this is?
Um...
Something to defeat bears with.
No.
That's the frame of a tent.
You hang the tent from the frame,
cover it with the fly,
fasten it,
and it's done.
Amazing!
Look how light it is!
Hey, let's go inside.
Aoi, you too!
It's so cramped!
If I don't do something, I really will have to climb a mountain.
Aoi, you didn't remember me, did you?
Thanks for hanging out with me when you didn't want to.
I was so happy, I just couldn't resist dragging you around.
It's beautiful.
I'm glad we saw it together.
I'll go to the mountain with my dad.
Watch carefully.
This is the most beautiful moment in the world.
An unforgettable memory.
Let's come here together again someday.
Yeah!
Definitely! Definitely!
That's right.
We went together, didn't we?
Aoi?
The words just fell out of my mouth naturally.
As long as it's not too high,
would it be okay if I went to the mountains?
Really?
Then let's go to Mt. Fuji!
Can we start with maybe a hill?
What about K2?
Everest?
Are you even listening to me?
All right!
I regret it a little.
ikou!
行こう!
Let's go!
sutakkaato mitai ni
スタッカートみたいに
Like a staccato
mune o tataku wakuwakukan
胸を叩くワクワク感
the feeling of excitement beats within my chest.
fushigi fuan yori
不思議 不安より
More than strange anxiety
tanoshimi no youryou ga fueta yo
楽しみの容量が増えたよ
my capacity for fun has increased.
mata ashita! yahhoo♪
また明日!ヤッホー♪
See you tomorrow! Yahoo♪